module.exports = [
    {
        front: "some front words",
        back: "some back words",
        deck_id: 2
    },
    {
        front: "some frosadsadant words",
        back: "some back worsadsds",
        deck_id: 3
    },
    {
        front: "sossssme front words",
        back: "soddddme back words",
        deck_id: 3
    },
    {
        front: "sdsadasdasdasdsaome front words",
        back: "some words",
        deck_id: 5
    },
    {
        front: "soddme frodfdfnt words",
        back: "some bafffffffffffffffck words",
        deck_id: 1
    },
    {
        front: "some frssont words",
        back: "some basdsdck words",
        deck_id: 4
    },
    {
        front: "some fronsdsdt words",
        back: "some back worsdsds",
        deck_id: 4
    },
    {
        front: "some font words",
        back: "s words",
        deck_id: 4
    },
    {
        front: "some fr######ont words",
        back: "some bac32323213k words",
        deck_id: 2
    },
    {
        front: "somedwdqdqwddwqd front wordqwdwqdwds",
        back: "some back zzzzzzzzzzzwords",
        deck_id: 1
    }
]